viikii.net 2012-08-03

# Viki.com

Revised: December 2, 2010

This Privacy Policy describes how VIKI, INC. ("we," “our” or "us") collects, uses and shares your information on our website at ViKi.com (collectively, the “Website”) We provide an online video service offering a selection of content and other services from time to time, which are referred to collectively as the "ViKi Services." Use of the ViKi Services is subject to our Terms of Service.

### Information We Collect

We collect information as follows. First, when you create an account on the Website, we collect personally identifiable information, including your name, email address, nationality and language, and, if you purchase services, credit and debit card information, PayPal information, mobile payment information and/or other payment information depending on the payment option you select. Second, we automatically collect information when you visit the Website or use the ViKi Services. We also automatically collect non- personally identifiable information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, software and hardware attributes, the page you request, and cookie and Web beacon information. Non-personal information means information that does not allow someone to identify you individually. 

### How we use information we collect

We use the information we collect about you for the following general purposes: (i) contacting you; (ii) customizing the content and advertising you view (iii) fulfilling your requests for products or services; (iv) identifying the comments you post on the Website; (v) improving the ViKi Services; (vi) conducting research; (vii) compiling aggregate data for internal and external business purposes; (viii) preventing potentially illegal activities; (ix) protecting our rights and other uses in accordance with our Terms of Service; and (x) for any other purpose disclosed to you at the time we collect your personally identifiable information. 

### Disclosure of information

We may share information that we have collected about you with other users if you voluntarily make the information public, including by (i) creating an account on the Website (whereby your account name and certain account information will be provided to other users of the Website), (ii) adding certain information to your channel page, and (iii) submitting videos or sending messages through the Website. 

Also, we may share personal information with companies and organizations that we hire/contract with to perform services for us (for example, processing credit and debit card, mobile and PayPal payments) 

In addition, we may disclose your personal information to comply with legal requirements, like law, regulation, warrant, subpoena, court order, or with a regulator or law enforcement agency or personnel, or in connection with a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, reorganization, dissolution or similar event. 

### Email addresses

If you have provided your email address on the Website and have opted in, we may send you emails informing you of any major changes to the Website, or any pertinent information about the content on ViKi.com. If you do not want to receive these emails, please make a change to your email preference in your ViKi.com profile page. 

### Choice and Access to Personal Information

We want to keep personal information accurate. To correct or update your personal information, please visit your account profile page. 

### Links to Other Web Sites

The Website may link to Web sites of other companies or organizations. These links are provided for your convenience. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these links. We do not control these Web sites and are not responsible for their operation or content. Please review the privacy policy for each Web site you visit. 

### Cookies and Web Beacons

Cookies are small data files that are sent to your Web browser and placed on your computer's hard drive when you visit a Web site. You can set your Web browser to accept or decline cookies. Some sections of our Web site may not work properly if you decline cookies. 

A Web beacon or similar means (collectively, "Pixel Tags") is a small string of code that provides a way for us to deliver a small graphic image (usually invisible) on a Web page or in an email. Pixel Tags can recognize certain types of information on your browser, check whether you have viewed a particular Web page or email message, and determine, among other things, the time and date on which you viewed the Pixel Tag and the IP address of the computer from which it was viewed. 

We use cookies, Pixel Tags and log file information to (i) store information so that you will not have to re- enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Website; (ii) provide custom, personalized content and information; (iii) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns and (iv) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc. 

### Third-party Advertisers

We permit advertisements to be delivered to you by third party Internet advertising companies (also called "ad networks" or "network advertisers"). These companies may use cookies, Web beacons and other technologies to collect non-personally identifiable information about your visits to the Website to deliver advertisements to you, measure their effectiveness and personalize advertising content. We do not have access to or control over cookies, Web beacons or other technologies that they may use. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of third party advertisers. You should check the privacy policy of the third party advertiser to determine how it handles any personally identifiable information it separately collects from you. Please be aware that we do not warn you when you have chosen to link through to another Web site or property from the Website. In addition, the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) offers information about Internet advertising companies, including about how to opt-out of their information collection. 

### Transfer of Information to Other Countries

Our processing of the information that it collects may involve the transfer of that information to various countries around the world. By submitting your information to us via the Website or in connection with your interactions with us offline, you consent to such transfers and to the processing of this information in various countries around the world. 

### Security

We take reasonable steps to protect personal information from loss and misuse. No Internet transmission is 100% secure. We use reasonable physical, technical, and administrative measures to safeguard personally identifiable information in our possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure, or modification. Some email sent to or from the Website may not be secure. Please consider this when sending information to us by email. 

### Children's Privacy

We do not intentionally collect personal information from children under age 13. If we discover that a child has provided us with personal information online through the Website, we will take reasonable steps to delete this information. If you believe we may have accidentally received personal information from a child under age 13, please immediately contact us at [privacy@viki.com](mailto:privacy@viki.com "privacy@viki.com") . 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may modify, alter or update this Privacy Policy at any time, so we encourage you to review this Privacy Policy frequently. We will not provide individual notice to you of changes to this Privacy Policy, but when we make updates to this Privacy Policy, we will update the last revised date set forth above. 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@viki.com](mailto:privacy@viki.com "privacy@viki.com") . 

### Fun in Any Language™

Viki is a global TV site, where millions of people watch their favorite shows, movies, music videos and more -- translated into 150+ languages by a community of avid fans. Together, we’re breaking down barriers that stand between great entertainment and its fans, no matter where they are! 

© 2010-2012 ViKi, Inc. All Rights Reserved. 

  * ### Viki World

  * About Us
  * Our Community
  * Our Partners
  * Mobile
  * Sitemap
  * Contact Us
  * Press
  * Jobs

  * ### Awards

  * TechCrunch: Best International Start-Up
  * DLD: Top 20 Internet Start-Up
  * SXSW Accelerator Finalist
  * Paley Center's 2011 Next Big Thing'

  * ### The Legal Stuff

  * The use of this website constitutes acceptance of the Viki terms of use and privacy policy. See also our intellectual property policy
